B E N F A N N I N G

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I am 24 year old politics graduate turned ski instructor turned full-stack developer. I attended Le Wagon coding bootcamp in 2017 Since then I have returned as a teaching assistant, where I spend time debugging code and explaining coding concepts to students. For more information, check out benfanning.co.uk.

CONTACT

07432495082 http://www.benfanning.co.uk/ fanninggg@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/benfanning-28523315b/

EXPERIENCE

TEACHING ASSISTANT | LE WAGON LONDON | MAR 2018 - PRESENT

- Gave me the opportunity to redouble my full-stack knowledge, as well as refining said knowledge through providing explanations of the finer points to students.
- Allowed me to review and debug code written in a number of different styles.

SKI INSTRUCTOR/SUPERVISOR | MT NORQUAY | OCT 2015 - MAY 2017

- Learned the joy of teaching a skill to others and the responsibility which comes with acting in loco parentis.
- Supervising 10 of my fellow instructors was a privilege which enabled me to greatly develop my management and leadership qualities.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Kennedy Club | St George's College | Weybridge, Surrey.

The SGC Kennedy Club is a student run organisation which helps care for members of the community with severe learning difficulties, in order to give full time carers a night off and provide an atmosphere worth looking forward to for the guests.

SKILLS

- RUBY
- RUBY ON RAILS
- HTML/CSS (SASS)
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS

EDUCATION

LE WAGON BOOTCAMP | LONDON | 2017 - 2018

- 9 week intensive program
- Covered the basics of Ruby, Software modelling, Database & SQL, Front End, Rails Framework & AirBnB project, Final project

UNIVERSITY OF PLYMOUTH | DEVON | 2012 - 2015

- Bachelor of Arts, 2:1
- Politics & International Relations